鸡胸肉好了
pick up chicken breast
我猜 你想要里面有硬硬东西的那种 对吧
the way I know you want it with the bone in
我觉得我们该开会讨论一下餐馆里的性骚扰问题了
we really should hold a seminar about sexual harassment in the work place
为啥 他一直都骚扰得很出色啊
why he is already so good at it
我很严肃的 如果每次被骚扰的是他他会怎么想
I'm serious how did he like it if we do that to him every time we order
试试看呗
well let's find out
点菜啦
ordering
一个五香薰牛肉
one pastrami
帅哥帮我个忙好不 把牛肉弄得又大又粗
can you do me a favor doll face make it so big
粗得嘴巴都含不住的
and thick you can’t get your mouth around it
可以么 帅哥
can you do that sweet heart
对 还有两碗丸子汤
yes and two matzo ball soups
小心拿那两颗丸子啊 等等 让我拿着那两颗"丸子"吧
hold the balls wait I’ll hold the balls
你坐稳了 享受就好
you just sit there and look pretty
还有奶油...
and  a cream of …
不行了 把我自己都膈应到了
no I can't  just gross myself out
什么时候你们才能骚一点儿啊
when is this gonna get dirty
破产姐妹   第一季    第十四集
天天美剧字幕组
本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业用途
=============================
时间轴 猫小七 雪域清廷
听译 安小姐 大Z 饺子 夏翊 羊羊 luca
校对 D- Raphael 黄鱼 猴子 露露 米兰 月球
=============================
Max 出来 (跟出柜是同一个词)
Max come out
如果我出柜肯定不是为你 是为那个有龙纹身的女孩
if I came out would not be for you be for that hot dragon tatoo girl
董事会成员 欢迎来到首届Max家制蛋糕
welcome board members to the very first financial assessment meeting
财政评估会
of the Max’s homemade cupcakes
有人告诉我会有一个奶酪拼盘
I was told there will be a cheese plate
经过5个月的经营 我们赢利725美元
after five months in business we are showing a profit of 725 dollors
不得不说我有点失望
I have to say I’m a little disappointed
真的 可是我觉得我们这5个月远远超出了我的想象啊
really cuz dude we have so far exceeded where I thought we’d be in 5 months
听着 我们得找一个更赚钱的兼职来补贴我们的生意
look we have to find a way to make more money on the side to put into the business
或者我们可以见好就收
or we could quit now where we are a success
说什么呢
what are you talking about
事情只会变得更糟
it’s only gonna get worse
或者可能会变得更好  你为什么一定要那么说呢
or it could get better  why would you even say that
因为那就是生活 是生活就会变得越来越糟
because that’s life and life gets worse that what it does
在生活的简历上 它的特殊技能就是擅长把事情弄糟
on life’s resume under special skills it says good at making things worse
你总是往最坏的情况去想么
do you always go to the worst case scenario
对 我的履历上写着擅长往最坏情况去想
yup on my resume it says good at going to the worst case scenario
你可以更乐观一点么  不要总把事情想得那么糟
do you think you could try to be more optimistic and not expect the worst all the time
谁啊
who's that
乐观些对吧
more optimistic right
我们把门打开就能看到你所有损失的钱
on the other side of that door is all the money you lost
然后我们搬回了你的联排别墅  换我在你的浴缸里自慰
and then we move back to your townhouse  I masturbate in your tub for a change
就两次 而且你本来应该敲门的
it was twice and you could have knocked
谁呀
who is it
纽约警局的警探 James
detective James NYPD
等一下 别开门 别开门
wait don’t open it don’t open it
哦 我星期二才抽呢 开吧
oh smoke day is Tuesday open
很抱歉打扰你  你是住这里么
sorry to bother you miss  you live in this apartment
我要向你坦白 警官 我们的名字不再租约上
I’m gonna tell you right now officer our names aren’t on the lease
我们是合法转租因为我们无处可去 请高抬贵手啊
we are in a legal sublet with no place else to go please mercy
不好意思警官 这孩子没见过世面
sorry officer it’s her first raid
别紧张 我和房东不是一伙的
relax the landlord didn’t send me
你对住在你楼上的房客有什么了解
what do you know about the tenant lives in the apartment directly above you
他叫 Lue?
his name is Lue?
Leo? Sal? 接近么
Leo? Sal?   Am I even close?
他叫Nahum Chhidori
his name is Nahum Chidori
哦 我连大陆板块都没猜对
oh man I wasn’t even on the right continent
那个是Nahum Chidori么
is that Nahum Chidori
死了两周了 自己住所以没人发现
been died for two weeks lived alone nobody knew
脸被猫吃了么
cats eat his face
Max 不要这么心理阴暗好吧
Max  could you please not  so dark
小猫咪吃了他的脸吗
kittens eat his face
咋啦 我只是我只是想试着阳光点
what  I’m just trying to put more positive spin on things
你拿着那个要去哪儿啊 那可我上好的蓝莓花瓷碟
where you going with that? that's my good china with huckleberry haunted on it
我做了一个你好的蛋糕拼盘给对面的邻居
I’m making a hello cupcake plate for our neighbors across the hall
不 你不是吧
no you are not
不认识自己的邻居多奇怪啊
it’s weird not to know your neighbors
不奇怪 不认识自己的爸才奇怪 不过等你到了4岁 这个就浮云了
no it’s weird not to know your father but by the time you are 4 you get over it and move on
这就是一个错误 谁知道门后潜伏着啥
this is a mistake who knows what’s lurking behind that door
是啊 有可怕的东西 比如一个会关照我们
yes something awful like nice people
会在走廊里和我们打招呼的好人
who might look out for us to say hello in the hallway when they see you
不管走出什么  我都不会在走廊里和陌生人说话
no matter what comes out of there I will not be helloing it up in the hallway
你走运了 赶紧给我回来
you got lucky get back in here
请问是谁啊
who is it please
你对面的邻居Caroline
Caroline your next door neighbor
我来的不是时候么
hi is this a bad time
不不不
not at all
- 一会就好  - 嗨
- one second  - hi
我和我室友Max是想来介绍下自己
I just want to introduce myself and my roommate Max
然后 这些蛋糕送给你
there and give you these cupcakes
你们人真好
that is so nice
没 这是我力锁...力所能及的
well it's the leash, leas..least I can do
好吧   我得走了
well  I get to go
起码我们知道养狗了该找谁去遛
well  if we ever get a dog we know who can walk it
听
listen
我知道啊  才过了几天 已经有人住到楼上了
I know it's only been a few days that somebody has moved in upstairs
而且他们还放音乐
and they are playing music
音乐还穿过地板到我耳朵里了
music is coming through the floor into my ears
都怪你
I blame you for this
当你敲对面门的时候你可能打开了去地狱的入口
when you knock on the door across the hall you might have open the portal to hell
那  你听这邪恶的音乐
there  you hear the devil music
我觉得可能是Bee Gees (知名老牌爱尔兰乐队)
think it's the Bee Gees
就是
exactly
还走路   走来走去还放歌
and walking walking and music
我们现在就要阻止一切发生
we have to stop this right now
才10点 大家有权利走来走去和放歌
it's ten o'clock   people are allowed to walk and play music
你对公寓生活的无知已经快要触发我的极限了
your lack of apartment knowledge is really starting to piss me off
我们要去给他点厉害瞧瞧
we have to show him right now
别和我们对着干 我要纸
not to screw with us   I need paper
你要干嘛 我意思是 除了过激行为
what do you doing   I mean besides overacting
写威胁信
writing a threatening note
如果我们不解决
if we don't shut this down now
接下来 就有人可能要在你家客厅举办奥斯卡
next thing you know someone's having an Acadmy Awards party in your living room
你想这样
is that what you want
还有陌生人发的"最佳玉米片"的迷你奥斯卡小金人
strangers passing out  mini Oscar statues that says best nachos
我有把黑枪 可以直接射穿地板打死你
I have an unregistered gun and can shoot you through the floor
这样是不是太过激了 Max
you're coming in really hard Max
我们不能把这张递出去
we're not giving in this
这会搞僵邻里气氛的
it will start a bad dynamic between us
天知道我是有多想那个不说话死翘翘的印度人
God how I miss the quiet dead Indian guy
好 我们敲了就跑
okay  we're gonna hit and run
哦 你说的是真跑
oh you mean run  literally
嘘 听好
shhh   listen
读字条 吓呆了
reading our note  freaking out
音乐停止 问题解决
music off   problem solve
撤退了 不用怀疑 不用怀疑
row's backed, never doubt  never doubt
走到门口
crossing to the front to the door
关上大门
closing the door
走下楼梯
coming down the stairs
怎么办
what do we do
搬走
move
他长什么样
what's he look like
他手指挡在猫眼上了
he's got his finger over the peek hole
哼哼 有种 开战 你退后
huh huh  okay  game on   back up
敢在我的楼盘里撒野 老娘弄死你信么
this is my building  I've got take it back
Max  这是现实生活 不是使命召唤现代战争三啊
Max  this is life   not Call of Duty Modern Warfare III
闪开
move
找死啊
what
这个好吓人好吓人的小条儿是啥意思
what is the meaning of this horrible horrible note
哇 你不是男的啊
oh you are not a man
你这什么问题啊
What kind of question is this
我看起来像个男的吗
do I look like a man
看起来不像 底下听着像
no but you crump around up there like a man
Max 好了啦
Max  please
这好吓人好吓人的小条儿是你们写的么
did you write this horrible horrible note
就是 怎么着
yes I did
我第一天搬来新家
first day in my new home
你们就给我这个好吓人好吓人的小条儿来威胁我
and  I'm given this horrible horrible note with threats
呃 我们不是想威胁你
well they are not actually threats
我要把你当猪一样宰了
I will get you like a hog
澄清下 我就是看了一眼那个小条儿
to be clear   I only scheme the note
计划赶不上变化快
everything was happening so fast
很明显 我们是没给这段邻居关系开个好头  请进来吧
listen we've obviously gotten off to a bad start   please come in
我为什么要进去
why would I want to come in
你们都给我好吓人好吓人的小条儿了…哇哦
with your horrible horrible  woo..
蛋糕乐园呀
cupcake land
是的 我们做一点小蛋糕的小生意
yes  we have a cupcake business
虽然才开始 但是做的还不错
we're just starting but doing well
蛋糕都是Max做的呢 跟人打个招呼呀 Max
Max is the baker  say hello  Max
我认识黑帮的人
I know people in the mob
她是Max 我叫Caroline 你叫什么名字？
that's Max  and  I'm Caroline  you are...?
Sophie  Kchinsky
你说的可是波兰口音？
is that  a Polish accent I'm detecting
是的
yes
我去过华沙 我爱死那里了
I visit  Warsaw once  and  I love it
哦 我恨得不行 满街的老鼠和拉皮条的
oh...  cuz I hate it, rats and pimps
你们怎么不请我吃一个蛋糕啊
why have you not yet offer me cupcake
你们给我这么个好吓人好吓人的小条条 最起码得补偿我下吧
it's the least thing you can do after a horrible  horrible note
哦 行啊 你要巧克力的还是香草?
oh  sure  choclate or vanilla?
都要
yes
为什么要如此阴郁的接待顾客?
why is such sour porce?
关于那个真不好意思
sorry about that
只是我们在附近的一家餐馆里每天工作很久
It's just we work long hours at the neighborhood diner
而Max还在打另一份工
and Max has another job as well
之后她回家里还要做小蛋糕
and then she comes home and she has to make cupcakes
哦哦哦 太好吃了
mummmm so good
这么愤怒的人是怎么做出如此好吃的东西的?
how could someone so angry makes something so sweet
她不是总是这样的
she is not always like this
是 我就是经常这样 去问问之前的房客就知道了
yeah I'm usually like this  just ask the previous tenant
噢 对了 你问不到了
oh wait, you can't
你们两个女孩就像这些小蛋糕一样
you know you two girls are like these capcakes
这个棕色的丰满紧实 这个浅色的软萌可爱
one is dark and heavy and one is light and fluffy
我还是更喜欢那个软萌的
I prefer the fluffy one
我想 我们已经说的很明确了
well I think we've made our point
不能有音乐和咚咚的踩地板声
no music no clumping
因为我会用枪穿过地板射杀你 谢谢你的造访
I'll shoot you through the floor  thanks for stopping by
哈哈 真高兴我们已经可以互相开玩笑了
haha oh god so glad we can joke with each other already
对于那个纸条我很抱歉 我们可以开始...
sorry about the note, can we start ...
你有香奈儿的唇膏   是呀
you have the Chanel allure lip gloss  yeah
你知道香奈儿
you know the Chanel
知道? 我爱死它了! 只是我买不起了
know? love! I can't afford it anymore
那你拿一个呗 姐在包里一抓一大把呢
oh take one, I got handfuls in my bag
真的? 噢 那太好了
oh really? oh that's so nice
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey
你是要我把你拴起来吗
do I have to put you on a leash?
嘿 不如我们重新开始
hey we start again
你拿走那只香奈儿 我打包带走更多的小蛋糕
you take a Chanel, and I take more cupcakes to go
喔 当然可以
oh sure
这就对了
yes
我就知道 那个贱人为了小蛋糕耍了我们
I knew it! bitch played us for capcakes
现在是凌晨三点 为什么你穿着衣服?
it's 3am. why are you dressed?
永远不要脱掉衣服因为士兵们不会
never took off my clothes cause soldiers don't
要在敌人袭击的时候做好准备
you should get ready when the enemy attack
好吧 你是对的 我错了
ok, you were right, I was wrong
为什么你有一把扫帚?
why do you have the broom?
因为我的弹指飞弹用光了?
cause I ran out of finger bullets?
等等 你会掉下来的
wait, you're gonna fall
我真不敢相信我们有一把扫帚
I can't believe we have a broom
这么久以来我都是拿着本《美国周刊》扫地的
all this time I've been sweeping with a US Weekly
我知道这会发生但是我当时什么都没说
I knew this would happen but I didn't say anything
因为你总说那些 "Max你总会想到最坏的情况"
cause you were all "Max the worst case scenerio "
怎么样 现在我们暴露出弱点了 你看
what  we showed weakness and now look
我说的"我们"其实指的是你
by we, I mean you
受死吧 偷小蛋糕的贼
deal with this, cupcake thief
就这样 重重的再来一次
yea, one more time and hard
好吧 这下她毁了我们的房子
ok, now she broke our house.
现在就是战争
we are in a war
有种就来啊 你以为老娘吃素的啊?
she wants a piece of me? she's gonna get it
我的高跟鞋呢
where are my heels?
她以为我是谁
I mean who does she think I am
一个随随便便就能被一只香奈儿收买的人吗
someone she can just buy off with a tube of Chanel?
当她提出的时候 你的腿的确跑的比你思考的快
well your legs did kinda snap back over your head pretty quick when she offered it
我以为你是送pizza的
I thought you were a man with pizza
你家里有个秋千
you have a porch swing in there
你甚至有电动香烟
you have an electric cigarette
你们两个女孩到底想干嘛
what is it you two girls want?
呃 我忘了
uh, I forgot
只是被秋千和一切弄晕了
just so thrilled by the swing and everthing
对了 是你在占我们便宜
oh you're taking advantage of us
在我们讨论过之后还放音乐
by still playing that music after we talked
你们对人家好刻薄 甜心们
you two are harshing, my marshmallow
那我只能打电话给我的房东亲亲Marvin
I'm gonna have to call my friend the landlord the Marvin
告诉他你们好可怕好可怕的纸条
tell him about the horrible horrible note
我的天啊 她是个妓女
oh my god she's a hooker
我一直在用一个妓女的唇膏
I've been using a hooker's lip gloss
她才不是妓女
she's not a hooker
那我就放心了
oh good
她太老了 一定是老鸨
she's too old. she's a madam
你是一直在用一个老鸨的唇膏啊
you've been using an old hooker's lip gloss
Max 快看我的嘴唇
max, look, my lip
哪儿有什么吗 我总觉得有点什么
is this something? i feel like i'm getting one.
再和你说最后一次 疱疹不可能在10小时内爆发的
for the last time, you cannot get a herpes break out in under 10 hours
你是对的 我现在的情况就是就是最坏的那种
you are right, now i'm jumping to the worst case scenario
说不定她的唇膏不是疱疹的温床
maybe her lip gloss wasn't a herpes breeding ground
说不定她就不是一个妓女
maybe she's not a prostitute.
说不定那些年轻少女并没有被逼良为娼
maybe those young girls weren't being held against their will
是呀 说不定她家只是有些夜不归宿的女人
yeah ,maybe she just has sleepovers
穿着性感睡衣在秋千上晃荡
with women on swings in their nighties.
你知道 就好像正常人会这么做一样
you know, like people do.
欢迎来到Williamsburg餐厅
welcome to Williamsburg dinner
请问您是几位呢
how many in your party
这是哪门子问题?
what kind of question is this?
一个 就我一个人不行吗
one, I'm my own party
我就坐这桌了
I'll take booth
看 那边那位是谁啊
now, now, who is that over there
我们楼上的新邻居
our new upstairs neighbor
Earl 你觉得她像不像妓女
Earl does she look like a prostitute to you
我一般不以貌取人
well I don't like to judge a book by its cover
但如果她是本书 别的书一定愿意付钱跟她上床
but if she was a book, she'd be the kind of that other books paid for sex
所以说她刚进来 Earl觉得她是妓女
so she just came in ,Earl think she's a hooker
现在我觉得我的嘴唇肿的跟Courtney Love似的(涅主唱柯本之妻,厚嘴)
and now my lip is feeling very Courtney Love
我请她一顿饭 但我们一定要把这事解决了
I invited her here for a free meal, we have to make this work out for us
像她上一次威胁要给她房主"亲亲"打电话这种事 绝不能再发生
last time she threatened to call her "friend" the landlord, and that can never happen.
我们是非法租客 我宁愿楼上吵点也不愿没地方住
we are illegal tenants, I'd rather have a noise roof over my head than no roof
你在一边听我说就好 你太生气 万一说出什么侮辱的话就不好了
let me do the talking, you are too upset, you might say something insulting
能说什么? "嗨 多谢你的唇膏
like what? "hi  thanks for the lip gloss
我下半辈子 可不知道得跟我男朋友解释多少回呢"
and the series of uncomfortable conversation with every lover I'll have the rest of my life?"
你不需要告诉他们 他们最终会发现的
you don't need to tell them, they will figure it out eventually
嗨 感谢你能来
hi, thanks for coming in
我喜欢你的制服诶
I like the uniforms
你前面重点很突出嘛
you fill up the front nicely,
你这个没胸的也不要紧 有短裙裙博眼球
and you with no boobs short short skirts
好聪明的丫头们
smart girls!
呃 我们只是想请你吃顿饭 顺便道个歉
ehh... we just wanted to offer you a free dinner as our way of apologying
所以 你准备好点餐了吗?
so  are you ready to order
这是哪门子问题?
what kind of question is this?
你们看到这份好吓人好吓人的菜单了吗
did you see this horrible horrible menu
在这种环境下我们哪儿能有愉快的对话呀
we can't have nice conversation here
明天我带你们俩姑娘去个好地方 我请客
tomorrow I take you to nice place, my treat
噢 你没必要那么做的
oh, you don't have to do that
不 不 我也想要道歉
no no I too want to apologize
那天你们离开之后 我的姑娘们说我对你们太刻薄了
you know after you two left the other night some of my girls said I was harsh on you
你的姑娘们?
your girls?
当然 那些姑娘都为我工作嘛
yes, all those girls work for me
请原谅我要去下洗手间去查看下我的嘴唇
excuse me, I have to go to the lady's room now look at my lips
谢谢你请我们吃饭
thank you so much for inviting us
你喜欢那个鲟子酱么
are you enjoying that beluga
嗯 太喜欢了 谢谢阿
emmmm, so much, thank you
我好久都没吃到过鱼子酱了
I haven't had caviar forever
唔
emmm
行动又比理智反应快了?
legs over you head much?
这么阴阳怪气的 你不喜欢鱼子酱?
so sourpuss. you don't like caviar?
不 我更喜欢奶酪汉堡
no I'm more a cheese burger kind of girl
这里很繁忙 服务生一定很赚钱吧
this place is busy the waiters must make a fortune
对啊 一晚能赚300  350
oh ya 300, 350 a night
你们呢 赚多少?
What do you girls make?
好的时候六十到八十一晚
60 to 80 on a good night
就这点钱 怎么能完成你蛋糕生意的梦想啊
and how do you expect you accomplish cupcake business on money like this?
我们才刚刚开始啊
well ,we are just starting out
可是这样的话你们永远也完不成
yes but at this rate it will take forever
你知道么 我也有伟大的理想
you know I too have big dream
我想要在波兰建一个滨湖的避暑山庄
I am building summer house by lake in Poland
你想看么?
you wanna see?
哦 你有照片么
oh you have pictures?
不 我有房子
no... I have house
这个是建筑师给的模型
this is model from the architect
无论在哪里我都随身带着它 来提醒我我的梦想
and I take it everywhere I am, to remember where I'm going
很酷
it's cool
像你们这样的女孩应该能赚更多的钱
see girls like you should be making more money
也许你们可以考虑来为我工作
maybe you could consider coming to work for me
Sophie 谢谢你昨天送来我公寓的女孩
Sophie thank you for sending girl to my apartment yesterday
哦 她干活了么
oh did she do the job
哦 做的前无古人的好啊
oh like no one ever before
躺在地板上 上上下下 上上下下的不停啊
down on the floors under over under again
呵呵 这就对了 我的姑娘们 不做到你满意决不离开
hoho yes well  my girls don't leave utill you are satisfied
也许她可以一周来两次
maybe she can come 2 times a week
你想她什么啥时候去 她都会去
she can come whenever you want her to come
这两位也是你的姑娘
are these two of your girls
我们刚才正讨论这个呢
well we were just discussing that
这妞看起来更能干啊
this one here looks like she can take a lot
嗯...谢谢夸奖?
eh... thanks?
我朋友Yati在吧台那边
my friend Yati is at the bar
既然他很需要你的服务 那就请吧
since the boy is in great need of your service, prosze
哦 是的 失陪一下
oh yes excuse me
还有...不要碰我的房子
and em...  don't touch my house
我真不敢相信她居然想勾搭我们去做小姐
I cannot believe she would actually consider asking us to be prostitutes.
就是啊! 勾我还成 怎么还搭上你啊
I know!I mean me I get it. but you, I don’t see it
你也听到刚才那个男的说了 我一看就特能干啊
You heard the guy. I look like I can take a lot.
Max 一点都不好笑
Max. It's not funny.
她的香奈儿唇膏指不定会传染疱疹给我的 还不够惨的吗
isn’t bad enough I may have got herpes from her Channel gloss?
当然我们是不会去做的
of cause we are not gonna do it.
但是拜托 一看你就不是做小姐的料啊
but come on, you 'd be a terrible hooker.
承让 我的确不是
thank you. I would be a terrible hooker.
因为我还有心 有梦想 我还希望有朝一日能结婚生孩子呢
I have a heart and soul and dreams and I want to fall in love and have a family.
你就承认了吧 你床上功夫不行
oh, just say it. you are bad in bed
我们还是走吧
let’s get out of here.
说真的 她以为我是什么样的女孩啊 贪图享乐卖身求荣?
I mean, really, who does she think I am, someone who would just sell myself to have nice things?
我再吃一口 咱们就走
let’s me just suck down a little more of this and we are off.
你要是现在就跑放她鸽子 那我们只有去住救济院啦
if you walk out of here now, we can just keep walking to the homeless shelter.
我宁愿无家可归也不要去做小姐
I'd rather be homeless than a hooker.
快坐下
just sit down.
好啦 刚才我们说到哪儿啦
ok. back to what we were discussing.
诶  谢谢
uhh… thanks.
谢谢你考虑我们 但这份工作我们还是不能接受
we appreciate the offer but we are going to pass.
不想实现你们的梦想了么
so you don't want to accomplish your dream.
诶 我倒不确定这俩是一件事儿
well. I'm not exactly sure those two thinks line up.
但是还是谢谢了
but thanks.
我还当你们是聪明的姑娘呢
I thought you were smart girls.
我们是很聪明
we are smart girls.
所以我们才不会为了达到目的出卖肉体
and smart girls don't have to sell their bodies to accomplish their goals.
不是说这样不行哈
not that there's anything wrong with that.
对你来说当然行了 只是我们・・・那什么
it works for you. but us… well.
她床上功夫太烂 我脾气又不好
she is bad in bed and I have a sour puss.
什么样的男人会买我们的账啊?
what guy wants to pay for that?
你们以为我是做小姐的啊?
you think I am prostitute?
没有 谁家里还没有女孩子穿着睡衣玩秋千的啊
no. everyone has swings with girls in pajamas.
这是我的名片
my business card.
上门清洁服务
home cleaning service.
她是做家政生意的
she runs a cleaning company.
Sophie的选择（和影片《苏菲的选择》同名）
Sophie’s Choice.
你知道这说明什么了
you realize what this means.
说明我们侮辱了一个辛苦工作还要帮我们完成梦想的女人
we insulted a hard-working woman who is trying to help us attain our goal?
对 而且我不会得疱疹啦
yes, and I don’t have herpes.
我要是早听你的就好了 认识邻居什么的就是一个大错误
I should have listened to you. meeting neighbor is a big mistake.
认识邻居还管人家叫小姐 错大发了
and meeting neighbors and calling them a prostitute. bigger mistake.
你把人家气走了 搞得我们自己付饭钱
plus we had to kick in 60 for the check
我们要怎么跟人家说啊
what can we possibly say to her?
说我们很抱歉 你再什么时候想放音乐都行
that we are sorry and please keep playing the Bee Gees day or night as long as she wants.
人连门都没开 你傻乐什么呀
not a good idea to be smiling right now.
一想到不会得疱疹我心里痛快啊
I’m just so happy that I don’t have herpes.
你好 我们来的不是时候吗?
hi, is this a bad time?
对 我正忙着跟布鲁克林每一个男人上床 拿肉换钱呢
yes. yes. I'm in the middle having sex for money with every man in Brooklyn.
你们俩死讨厌死讨厌的丫头想干嘛
what your horrible horrible girls want?
给你 你梦想的碎片掉在桌子上了
here, you left part of your dream on the table.
我们真心道歉 我这也是第一次试着和邻居交往
and we want to apologize. I am new with this whole being neighborly thing
好吧 那这个软妹子还有什么说的
and what does the fluffy one have to say?
谢谢你对我们这么大方
thank you for being so generous
还想办法帮我们赚多钱去实现梦想
and for offering to help us make more money to accomplish our dream.
你以为说这两句就算完事儿啦
and this is supposed to make me feel better?
你们说我是小姐诶
you called me prostitute.
其实我们那也是在夸您美艳惊人
actually it's kind of a compliment that we thought you were stunning enough
男人们为了一亲你的芳泽不惜一掷千金啊
that man would pay to have sex with you
那倒是真的
this is true.
进来吧
come on in.
周末夜狂热是我最喜欢的电影
Saturday Night Fever is my favorite movie.
看那男的 性感到爆
look at him. he is so sexy.
他还好啦 还有点油头滑脑的
he is not that cute, kind of oily.
你说对了 她要做小姐那还不赔的跟孙子似的
you are right. she will make a terrible prostitute.
你家电视真给力
it’s a nice TV.
那当然 崭新的
yah, brand new.
过几天我要请我公司的女孩子们来看 通宵派对
I have all my girls over the other night for viewing Sleepover Party.
还是3D的呢
it’s also 3D
买电视送3D眼镜的吗
does it come with 3D glasses?
有啊 在那边抽屉里
yes, in the drawer there.
给
here.
Max 这又不是3D电影
Max. it’s not a 3D movie.
管它呢 这是3D眼镜就行了
who cares? it’s 3D glasses.
拜托 你不是成天在说要换个角度看世界吗
come on. you're always talking about one has to see things differently.
哇 酷毙啊
wow… so cool.
装秋千这主意真棒
this swing is a brilliant idea.
当然 准备装在我湖景豪宅的前廊上的
yah,it's for my porch at lake house..
但是何必要等那么久呢
but why wait.
现在不是享受梦想的好时光吗
dream is now.